# **Qi Dang**

Phone: (250) 891-2068

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/</a>

Email: <a href="mailto:qid14@outlook.com">qid14@outlook.com</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories">https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories</a>

# **Profile**

Passionate about software development. My entrepreneurial background has taught me strong interpersonal, and problem-solving skill, and persistence. BCIT CIT program has given me broad technology skill set including software & web development, cloud computing, database design/management, Windows & Linux system administration, and networking. My skill set was enhanced during my 16-months Co-op experience.

<b>Technical Skills</b>	5				
<ul><li>Programming</li><li>Python</li><li>Java</li></ul>	<ul><li>Web</li><li>JavaScript</li><li>HTML</li><li>CSS</li><li>NodeJS</li><li>ExpressJS</li></ul>	<ul><li>Frameworks</li><li>Flask</li><li>Bootstrap</li><li>Unittest</li><li>Django</li><li>ReactJS</li></ul>	• AWS • GCP • Azure	<ul><li>Database</li><li>MySQL</li><li>PostgreSQL</li><li>Firebase</li><li>MongoDB</li></ul>	Tools  Git  Jira  TeamCity  Linux/UNIX  Postman  Terraform  Docker  Ansible

# **Work Experience**

# **Associate Software Developer Co-op**

**HP** Teradici

- Developed and maintained Terraform, Bash, PowerShell, and Python cloud deployment scripts for AWS and GCP
- Utilized public clouds Google Cloud Platform and Amazon Web Services
- Integrated cloud logging and monitoring services to improve efficiency for troubleshooting and scaling on AWS and GCP
- Analyzed and resolved issues independently and with peers
- Provided support to other staff using the cloud deployment scripts

# Junior Systems Engineer & Back End Developer Co-op

May 2021 – August 2021

September 2021 - August 2022

Intellyon Inc.

- Developed and maintained cloud infrastructure on AWS, improved server availability and secured with customized firewall
- Developed REST APIs and ensured the requirements were met
- Collaborated with other peers on the improvement of software performance and performed error analysis
- Streamlined and automated code deployment process using bash scripts

# **Owner/ Store Manager**

April 2018 – April 2020

Tomley's Market

- Responded to customers' inquiries, complaints, and requirements in timely and professional manner
- Originated weekly planning including employee schedule, delivery schedule, stock management
- Monitored sales and revenue to ensure reaching the target each month and even surpassing it

# **Qi Dang**

Phone: (250) 891-2068

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/</a>

Email: <a href="mailto:qid14@outlook.com">qid14@outlook.com</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories">https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories</a>

- Hired new employees, instructed them in work safety standards and introduced them in the collective
- Placed orders and kept in contact with suppliers to ensure a great collaboration

# **Education**

#### British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver, BC

Computer Information Technology - GPA: 88%

### Camosun College, Victoria, BC

• Associate of Science Degree

## University of Victoria, Victoria, BC

Computer Science

# Jan 2018 – April 2018

Expected Graduation: Dec 2022

Winter 2020 - Present

Sept 2016 - Dec 2017

# **Personal Project**

### **Snake Game**

Duration: 3 days

- Developed a snake game which player has control over the snake to collect apple; then the scores are uploaded to a web leaderboard
- Developed the game using Python, Pygame, MySQL, and Flask
- Developed difficult levels to adjust speed of snake and score per apple

## **Academic Projects**

# **Inventory Management System**

Service Based Architectures

September 2022 – December 2022 (In progress)

- Developing an inventory management system in event-driven microservice architecture
- Developing the system using Python, MySQL, Kafka, Docker, SwaggerHub, and OpenAPI
- The system will be deployed on Microsoft Azure

#### **Scheduler**

Industry Sponsored Student Projects - This project is on trial in the NICU at BC Women's Hospital January 2021 – April 2021

- Expanded and improved a web-based application provides better schedule functions based on nurse's discipline, patient needs, and consistency of shift assignments
- The application was developed using Python, Flask, Jinja, jQuery, Bootstrap, and MySQL
- Developed on algorithms to make more accurate assignments
- Implemented filtered dropdown lists to anticipate conflicts in assignments
- Applied Agile methodology and built relationship with team members and clients

### **Maze Game**

Object-oriented Programming

# **Qi Dang**

Phone: (250) 891-2068 Email: gid14@outlook.com LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-dang/</a> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories">https://github.com/QI-D?tab=repositories</a>

### October 2020 - November 2020

- Developed a maze game that player has control over the character to explore the maze and collect items within duration; then the results are uploaded to a web leaderboard
- Developed the game using Python language, Pygame module and Model-view-controller pattern
- Developed and debugged the game with Test-driven Development process using pytest
- Applied Agile methodology and built relationship with team members
- Collaborated with team members on GitHub such as creating, pulling, pushing, and merging branches and resolved merge conflicts

#### **Social Reminder**

# **Developing Web Applications**

October 2020 - November 2020

- Developed a reminder app that enables user account creations, reminder creation, reminder modification and deletion. It also allows user to share reminders with friends.
- Developed the app using JavaScript language, NodeJS, ExpressJS, EJS, Bootstrap and MongoDB
- Established cookie session which stores credentials to maintain an active session for users
- Collaborated with three team members using Agile methodology and manage repository on GitHub